[
 {
	"QuestionID" : 220,
	"Question" : "What is (1 + 6) X 8 + 5?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (one plus six) times eight plus five?",
	"Answer" : 61,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is sixty-one.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 91,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by eight next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 54,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding one and six.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 1 to 6 before multiplying 8 with that sum, and then add 5 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "1 + 6 = 7; Now we have: 7 X 8 + 5; 7 X 8 = 56; Now we have 56 + 5 = 61"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 221,
	"Question" : "What is 9 + 5 X 0 + 6 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is nine plus five times zero plus six times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 9,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is nine.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 0,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply five by zero and six by zero",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 5 by 0 and 6 by 0, and add the second product to the first. Then, add 9 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 X 0 = 0; 6 X 0 = 0; Now we have 9 + 0 + 0; 9 + 0 = 9; Now we have 9 + 0 = 9"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 222,
	"Question" : "What is 4 + (0 + 5) X 9?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is four plus (zero plus five) times nine?", 
	"Answer" : 49,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is forty-nine.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 81,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by nine next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 49,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding zero and five.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 0 to 5 before multiplying 9 with that sum, and then add 4 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "0 + 5 = 5; Now we have:4 + 5 X 9; 5 X 9 = 45; Now we have 4 + 45 = 49"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 223,
	"Question" : "What is 3 + 7 X 4 - 6 X 2?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is three plus seven times four minus six times two?", 
	"Answer" : 19,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is nineteen.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 28,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply seven by four and six by two",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 7 by 4 and 6 by 2, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 3 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "7 X 4 = 28; 6 X 2 = 12; Now we have 3 + 28 - 12; 3 + 28 = 31; Now we have 31 - 12 = 19"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 224,
	"Question" : "What is (1 + 5) X 2 + 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (one plus five) times two plus three?",
	"Answer" : 15,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fifteen.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 30,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by two next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 14,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding one and five.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 1 to 5 before multiplying 2 with that sum, and then add 3 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "1 + 5 = 6; Now we have: 6 X 2 + 3; 6 X 2 = 12; Now we have 12 + 3 = 15"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 225,
	"Question" : "What is 2 + 7 X 4 + 7 X 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is two plus seven times four plus seven times four?", 
	"Answer" : 58,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fifty-eight.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 64,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply seven by four and seven by four",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 7 by 4 and 7 by 4, and add the second product to the first. Then, add 2 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "7 X 4 = 28; 7 X 4 = 28; Now we have 2 + 28 + 28; 2 + 28 = 30; Now we have 30 + 28 = 58"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 226,
	"Question" : "What is (0 + 8) X 4 + 5?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (zero plus eight) times four plus five?",
	"Answer" : 37,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is thirty-seven.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 72,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by four next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 37,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding zero and eight.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 0 to 8 before multiplying 4 with that sum, and then add 5 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "0 + 8 = 8; Now we have: 8 X 4 + 5; 8 X 4 = 32; Now we have 32 + 5 = 37"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 227,
	"Question" : "What is 9 + 9 X 4 - 5 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is nine plus nine times four minus five times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 45,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is forty-five.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 72,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply nine by four and five by zero",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 9 by 4 and 5 by 0, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 9 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 X 4 = 36; 5 X 0 = 0; Now we have 9 + 36 - 0; 9 + 36 = 45; Now we have 45 - 0 = 45"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 228,
	"Question" : "What is 6 + (0 + 8) X 7?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is six plus (zero plus eight) times seven?", 
	"Answer" : 62,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is sixty-two.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 98,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by seven next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 62,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding zero and eight.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 0 to 8 before multiplying 7 with that sum, and then add 6 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "0 + 8 = 8; Now we have:6 + 8 X 7; 8 X 7 = 56; Now we have 6 + 56 = 62"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 229,
	"Question" : "What is 8 + 9 X 1 + 7 X 2?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is eight plus nine times one plus seven times two?", 
	"Answer" : 31,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is thirty-one.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 31,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply nine by one and seven by two",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 9 by 1 and 7 by 2, and add the second product to the first. Then, add 8 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 X 1 = 9; 7 X 2 = 14; Now we have 8 + 9 + 14; 8 + 9 = 17; Now we have 17 + 14 = 31"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 230,
	"Question" : "What is (1 + 8) X 0 + 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (one plus eight) times zero plus one?",
	"Answer" : 1,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is one.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 9,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by zero next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 2,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding one and eight.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 1 to 8 before multiplying 0 with that sum, and then add 1 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "1 + 8 = 9; Now we have: 9 X 0 + 1; 9 X 0 = 0; Now we have 0 + 1 = 1"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 231,
	"Question" : "What is 5 + 6 X 1 - 8 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is five plus six times one minus eight times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 11,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is eleven.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 11,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply six by one and eight by zero",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 6 by 1 and 8 by 0, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 5 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 X 1 = 6; 8 X 0 = 0; Now we have 5 + 6 - 0; 5 + 6 = 11; Now we have 11 - 0 = 11"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 232,
	"Question" : "What is 1 + (0 + 7) X 7?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is one plus (zero plus seven) times seven?", 
	"Answer" : 50,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fifty.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 56,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by seven next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 50,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding zero and seven.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 0 to 7 before multiplying 7 with that sum, and then add 1 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "0 + 7 = 7; Now we have:1 + 7 X 7; 7 X 7 = 49; Now we have 1 + 49 = 50"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 233,
	"Question" : "What is 2 + 6 X 0 + 5 X 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is two plus six times zero plus five times four?", 
	"Answer" : 22,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-two.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 20,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply six by zero and five by four",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 6 by 0 and 5 by 4, and add the second product to the first. Then, add 2 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 X 0 = 0; 5 X 4 = 20; Now we have 2 + 0 + 20; 2 + 0 = 2; Now we have 2 + 20 = 22"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 234,
	"Question" : "What is (0 + 7) X 8 + 5?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (zero plus seven) times eight plus five?",
	"Answer" : 61,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is sixty-one.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 91,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by eight next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 61,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding zero and seven.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 0 to 7 before multiplying 8 with that sum, and then add 5 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "0 + 7 = 7; Now we have: 7 X 8 + 5; 7 X 8 = 56; Now we have 56 + 5 = 61"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 235,
	"Question" : "What is 4 + 6 X 0 + 9 X 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is four plus six times zero plus nine times one?", 
	"Answer" : 13,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is thirteen.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 9,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply six by zero and nine by one",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 6 by 0 and 9 by 1, and add the second product to the first. Then, add 4 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 X 0 = 0; 9 X 1 = 9; Now we have 4 + 0 + 9; 4 + 0 = 4; Now we have 4 + 9 = 13"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 236,
	"Question" : "What is (0 + 5) X 4 + 6?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (zero plus five) times four plus six?",
	"Answer" : 26,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-six.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 50,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by four next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 26,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding zero and five.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 0 to 5 before multiplying 4 with that sum, and then add 6 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "0 + 5 = 5; Now we have: 5 X 4 + 6; 5 X 4 = 20; Now we have 20 + 6 = 26"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 237,
	"Question" : "What is 4 + 6 X 2 - 7 X 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is four plus six times two minus seven times one?", 
	"Answer" : 9,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is nine.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 13,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply six by two and seven by one",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 6 by 2 and 7 by 1, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 4 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 X 2 = 12; 7 X 1 = 7; Now we have 4 + 12 - 7; 4 + 12 = 16; Now we have 16 - 7 = 9"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 238,
	"Question" : "What is (2 + 7) X 2 + 2?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (two plus seven) times two plus two?",
	"Answer" : 20,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 36,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by two next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 18,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding two and seven.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 2 to 7 before multiplying 2 with that sum, and then add 2 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "2 + 7 = 9; Now we have: 9 X 2 + 2; 9 X 2 = 18; Now we have 18 + 2 = 20"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 239,
	"Question" : "What is 9 + 6 X 1 + 5 X 2?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is nine plus six times one plus five times two?", 
	"Answer" : 25,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-five.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 25,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply six by one and five by two",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 6 by 1 and 5 by 2, and add the second product to the first. Then, add 9 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 X 1 = 6; 5 X 2 = 10; Now we have 9 + 6 + 10; 9 + 6 = 15; Now we have 15 + 10 = 25"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 240,
	"Question" : "What is 7 + (1 + 8) X 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is seven plus (one plus eight) times one?", 
	"Answer" : 16,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is sixteen.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 16,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by one next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 16,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding one and eight.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 1 to 8 before multiplying 1 with that sum, and then add 7 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "1 + 8 = 9; Now we have:7 + 9 X 1; 9 X 1 = 9; Now we have 7 + 9 = 16"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 241,
	"Question" : "What is 8 + 5 X 3 - 9 X 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is eight plus five times three minus nine times one?", 
	"Answer" : 14,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fourteen.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 30,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply five by three and nine by one",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 5 by 3 and 9 by 1, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 8 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 X 3 = 15; 9 X 1 = 9; Now we have 8 + 15 - 9; 8 + 15 = 23; Now we have 23 - 9 = 14"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 242,
	"Question" : "What is 7 + (3 + 6) X 9?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is seven plus (three plus six) times nine?", 
	"Answer" : 88,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is eighty-eight.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 144,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by nine next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 64,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding three and six.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 3 to 6 before multiplying 9 with that sum, and then add 7 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 + 6 = 9; Now we have:7 + 9 X 9; 9 X 9 = 81; Now we have 7 + 81 = 88"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 243,
	"Question" : "What is 9 + 9 X 1 - 5 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is nine plus nine times one minus five times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 18,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is eighteen.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 18,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply nine by one and five by zero",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 9 by 1 and 5 by 0, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 9 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 X 1 = 9; 5 X 0 = 0; Now we have 9 + 9 - 0; 9 + 9 = 18; Now we have 18 - 0 = 18"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 244,
	"Question" : "What is (3 + 6) X 4 + 8?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (three plus six) times four plus eight?",
	"Answer" : 44,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is forty-four.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 108,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by four next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 35,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding three and six.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 3 to 6 before multiplying 4 with that sum, and then add 8 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 + 6 = 9; Now we have: 9 X 4 + 8; 9 X 4 = 36; Now we have 36 + 8 = 44"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 245,
	"Question" : "What is 4 + 9 X 3 - 7 X 2?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is four plus nine times three minus seven times two?", 
	"Answer" : 17,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is seventeen.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 25,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply nine by three and seven by two",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 9 by 3 and 7 by 2, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 4 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 X 3 = 27; 7 X 2 = 14; Now we have 4 + 27 - 14; 4 + 27 = 31; Now we have 31 - 14 = 17"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 246,
	"Question" : "What is (2 + 5) X 0 + 9?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (two plus five) times zero plus nine?",
	"Answer" : 9,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is nine.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 63,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by zero next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 11,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding two and five.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 2 to 5 before multiplying 0 with that sum, and then add 9 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "2 + 5 = 7; Now we have: 7 X 0 + 9; 7 X 0 = 0; Now we have 0 + 9 = 9"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 247,
	"Question" : "What is 4 + 6 X 2 - 8 X 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is four plus six times two minus eight times one?", 
	"Answer" : 8,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is eight.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 12,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply six by two and eight by one",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 6 by 2 and 8 by 1, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 4 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 X 2 = 12; 8 X 1 = 8; Now we have 4 + 12 - 8; 4 + 12 = 16; Now we have 16 - 8 = 8"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 248,
	"Question" : "What is 2 + (0 + 7) X 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is two plus (zero plus seven) times three?", 
	"Answer" : 23,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-three.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 27,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by three next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 23,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding zero and seven.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 0 to 7 before multiplying 3 with that sum, and then add 2 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "0 + 7 = 7; Now we have:2 + 7 X 3; 7 X 3 = 21; Now we have 2 + 21 = 23"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 249,
	"Question" : "What is 6 + 5 X 3 - 5 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is six plus five times three minus five times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 21,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-one.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 33,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply five by three and five by zero",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 5 by 3 and 5 by 0, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 6 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 X 3 = 15; 5 X 0 = 0; Now we have 6 + 15 - 0; 6 + 15 = 21; Now we have 21 - 0 = 21"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 250,
	"Question" : "What is 1 + (2 + 7) X 9?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is one plus (two plus seven) times nine?", 
	"Answer" : 82,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is eighty-two.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 90,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by nine next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 66,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding two and seven.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 2 to 7 before multiplying 9 with that sum, and then add 1 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "2 + 7 = 9; Now we have:1 + 9 X 9; 9 X 9 = 81; Now we have 1 + 81 = 82"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 251,
	"Question" : "What is 2 + 5 X 0 + 6 X 2?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is two plus five times zero plus six times two?", 
	"Answer" : 14,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fourteen.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 12,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply five by zero and six by two",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 5 by 0 and 6 by 2, and add the second product to the first. Then, add 2 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 X 0 = 0; 6 X 2 = 12; Now we have 2 + 0 + 12; 2 + 0 = 2; Now we have 2 + 12 = 14"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 252,
	"Question" : "What is 0 + (2 + 6) X 9?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is zero plus (two plus six) times nine?", 
	"Answer" : 72,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is seventy-two.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 72,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by nine next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 56,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding two and six.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 2 to 6 before multiplying 9 with that sum, and then add 0 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "2 + 6 = 8; Now we have:0 + 8 X 9; 8 X 9 = 72; Now we have 0 + 72 = 72"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 253,
	"Question" : "What is 9 + 7 X 0 + 9 X 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is nine plus seven times zero plus nine times one?", 
	"Answer" : 18,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is eighteen.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 9,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply seven by zero and nine by one",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 7 by 0 and 9 by 1, and add the second product to the first. Then, add 9 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "7 X 0 = 0; 9 X 1 = 9; Now we have 9 + 0 + 9; 9 + 0 = 9; Now we have 9 + 9 = 18"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 254,
	"Question" : "What is 0 + (3 + 5) X 9?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is zero plus (three plus five) times nine?", 
	"Answer" : 72,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is seventy-two.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 72,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by nine next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 48,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding three and five.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 3 to 5 before multiplying 9 with that sum, and then add 0 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 + 5 = 8; Now we have:0 + 8 X 9; 8 X 9 = 72; Now we have 0 + 72 = 72"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 255,
	"Question" : "What is 1 + 6 X 3 + 6 X 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is one plus six times three plus six times four?", 
	"Answer" : 43,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is forty-three.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 45,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply six by three and six by four",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 6 by 3 and 6 by 4, and add the second product to the first. Then, add 1 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 X 3 = 18; 6 X 4 = 24; Now we have 1 + 18 + 24; 1 + 18 = 19; Now we have 19 + 24 = 43"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 256,
	"Question" : "What is 2 + (1 + 6) X 5?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is two plus (one plus six) times five?", 
	"Answer" : 37,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is thirty-seven.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 45,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by five next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 33,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding one and six.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 1 to 6 before multiplying 5 with that sum, and then add 2 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "1 + 6 = 7; Now we have:2 + 7 X 5; 7 X 5 = 35; Now we have 2 + 35 = 37"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 257,
	"Question" : "What is 9 + 7 X 0 + 5 X 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is nine plus seven times zero plus five times four?", 
	"Answer" : 29,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-nine.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 20,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply seven by zero and five by four",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 7 by 0 and 5 by 4, and add the second product to the first. Then, add 9 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "7 X 0 = 0; 5 X 4 = 20; Now we have 9 + 0 + 20; 9 + 0 = 9; Now we have 9 + 20 = 29"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 258,
	"Question" : "What is 1 + (3 + 5) X 9?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is one plus (three plus five) times nine?", 
	"Answer" : 73,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is seventy-three.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 81,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by nine next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 49,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding three and five.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 3 to 5 before multiplying 9 with that sum, and then add 1 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 + 5 = 8; Now we have:1 + 8 X 9; 8 X 9 = 72; Now we have 1 + 72 = 73"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 259,
	"Question" : "What is 5 + 9 X 3 + 7 X 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is five plus nine times three plus seven times four?", 
	"Answer" : 60,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is sixty.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 70,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply nine by three and seven by four",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 9 by 3 and 7 by 4, and add the second product to the first. Then, add 5 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 X 3 = 27; 7 X 4 = 28; Now we have 5 + 27 + 28; 5 + 27 = 32; Now we have 32 + 28 = 60"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 260,
	"Question" : "What is (0 + 9) X 4 + 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (zero plus nine) times four plus three?",
	"Answer" : 39,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is thirty-nine.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 63,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by four next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 39,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding zero and nine.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 0 to 9 before multiplying 4 with that sum, and then add 3 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "0 + 9 = 9; Now we have: 9 X 4 + 3; 9 X 4 = 36; Now we have 36 + 3 = 39"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 261,
	"Question" : "What is 1 + 5 X 3 + 5 X 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is one plus five times three plus five times three?", 
	"Answer" : 31,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is thirty-one.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 33,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply five by three and five by three",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 5 by 3 and 5 by 3, and add the second product to the first. Then, add 1 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 X 3 = 15; 5 X 3 = 15; Now we have 1 + 15 + 15; 1 + 15 = 16; Now we have 16 + 15 = 31"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 262,
	"Question" : "What is 4 + (4 + 5) X 7?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is four plus (four plus five) times seven?", 
	"Answer" : 67,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is sixty-seven.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 91,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by seven next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 43,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding four and five.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 4 to 5 before multiplying 7 with that sum, and then add 4 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "4 + 5 = 9; Now we have:4 + 9 X 7; 9 X 7 = 63; Now we have 4 + 63 = 67"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 263,
	"Question" : "What is 8 + 6 X 1 - 6 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is eight plus six times one minus six times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 14,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fourteen.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 14,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply six by one and six by zero",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 6 by 1 and 6 by 0, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 8 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 X 1 = 6; 6 X 0 = 0; Now we have 8 + 6 - 0; 8 + 6 = 14; Now we have 14 - 0 = 14"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 264,
	"Question" : "What is (2 + 6) X 2 + 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (two plus six) times two plus three?",
	"Answer" : 19,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is nineteen.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 40,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by two next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 17,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding two and six.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 2 to 6 before multiplying 2 with that sum, and then add 3 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "2 + 6 = 8; Now we have: 8 X 2 + 3; 8 X 2 = 16; Now we have 16 + 3 = 19"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 265,
	"Question" : "What is 6 + 8 X 4 - 6 X 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is six plus eight times four minus six times three?", 
	"Answer" : 20,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 38,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply eight by four and six by three",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 8 by 4 and 6 by 3, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 6 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "8 X 4 = 32; 6 X 3 = 18; Now we have 6 + 32 - 18; 6 + 32 = 38; Now we have 38 - 18 = 20"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 266,
	"Question" : "What is 7 + (0 + 7) X 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is seven plus (zero plus seven) times one?", 
	"Answer" : 14,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fourteen.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 14,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by one next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 14,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding zero and seven.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 0 to 7 before multiplying 1 with that sum, and then add 7 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "0 + 7 = 7; Now we have:7 + 7 X 1; 7 X 1 = 7; Now we have 7 + 7 = 14"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 267,
	"Question" : "What is 1 + 9 X 3 - 8 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is one plus nine times three minus eight times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 28,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-eight.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 30,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply nine by three and eight by zero",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 9 by 3 and 8 by 0, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 1 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 X 3 = 27; 8 X 0 = 0; Now we have 1 + 27 - 0; 1 + 27 = 28; Now we have 28 - 0 = 28"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 268,
	"Question" : "What is (2 + 7) X 0 + 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (two plus seven) times zero plus three?",
	"Answer" : 3,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is three.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 27,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by zero next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 5,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding two and seven.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 2 to 7 before multiplying 0 with that sum, and then add 3 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "2 + 7 = 9; Now we have: 9 X 0 + 3; 9 X 0 = 0; Now we have 0 + 3 = 3"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 269,
	"Question" : "What is 1 + 5 X 0 + 7 X 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is one plus five times zero plus seven times one?", 
	"Answer" : 8,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is eight.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 7,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply five by zero and seven by one",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 5 by 0 and 7 by 1, and add the second product to the first. Then, add 1 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 X 0 = 0; 7 X 1 = 7; Now we have 1 + 0 + 7; 1 + 0 = 1; Now we have 1 + 7 = 8"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 270,
	"Question" : "What is 7 + (1 + 8) X 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is seven plus (one plus eight) times three?", 
	"Answer" : 34,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is thirty-four.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 48,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by three next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 32,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding one and eight.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 1 to 8 before multiplying 3 with that sum, and then add 7 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "1 + 8 = 9; Now we have:7 + 9 X 3; 9 X 3 = 27; Now we have 7 + 27 = 34"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 271,
	"Question" : "What is 4 + 6 X 4 - 7 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is four plus six times four minus seven times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 28,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-eight.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 40,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply six by four and seven by zero",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 6 by 4 and 7 by 0, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 4 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 X 4 = 24; 7 X 0 = 0; Now we have 4 + 24 - 0; 4 + 24 = 28; Now we have 28 - 0 = 28"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 272,
	"Question" : "What is (1 + 6) X 0 + 5?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (one plus six) times zero plus five?",
	"Answer" : 5,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is five.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 35,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by zero next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 6,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding one and six.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 1 to 6 before multiplying 0 with that sum, and then add 5 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "1 + 6 = 7; Now we have: 7 X 0 + 5; 7 X 0 = 0; Now we have 0 + 5 = 5"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 273,
	"Question" : "What is 0 + 9 X 4 - 9 X 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is zero plus nine times four minus nine times one?", 
	"Answer" : 27,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-seven.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 27,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply nine by four and nine by one",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 9 by 4 and 9 by 1, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 0 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 X 4 = 36; 9 X 1 = 9; Now we have 0 + 36 - 9; 0 + 36 = 36; Now we have 36 - 9 = 27"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 274,
	"Question" : "What is 7 + (2 + 5) X 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is seven plus (two plus five) times one?", 
	"Answer" : 14,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fourteen.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 14,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by one next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 14,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding two and five.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 2 to 5 before multiplying 1 with that sum, and then add 7 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "2 + 5 = 7; Now we have:7 + 7 X 1; 7 X 1 = 7; Now we have 7 + 7 = 14"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 275,
	"Question" : "What is 2 + 8 X 1 + 6 X 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is two plus eight times one plus six times four?", 
	"Answer" : 34,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is thirty-four.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 34,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply eight by one and six by four",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 8 by 1 and 6 by 4, and add the second product to the first. Then, add 2 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "8 X 1 = 8; 6 X 4 = 24; Now we have 2 + 8 + 24; 2 + 8 = 10; Now we have 10 + 24 = 34"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 276,
	"Question" : "What is (0 + 6) X 0 + 6?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (zero plus six) times zero plus six?",
	"Answer" : 6,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is six.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 36,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by zero next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 6,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding zero and six.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 0 to 6 before multiplying 0 with that sum, and then add 6 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "0 + 6 = 6; Now we have: 6 X 0 + 6; 6 X 0 = 0; Now we have 0 + 6 = 6"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 277,
	"Question" : "What is 1 + 9 X 2 - 9 X 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is one plus nine times two minus nine times one?", 
	"Answer" : 10,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is ten.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 11,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply nine by two and nine by one",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 9 by 2 and 9 by 1, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 1 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 X 2 = 18; 9 X 1 = 9; Now we have 1 + 18 - 9; 1 + 18 = 19; Now we have 19 - 9 = 10"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 278,
	"Question" : "What is (0 + 7) X 8 + 6?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (zero plus seven) times eight plus six?",
	"Answer" : 62,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is sixty-two.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 98,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by eight next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 62,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding zero and seven.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 0 to 7 before multiplying 8 with that sum, and then add 6 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "0 + 7 = 7; Now we have: 7 X 8 + 6; 7 X 8 = 56; Now we have 56 + 6 = 62"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 279,
	"Question" : "What is 3 + 6 X 2 - 6 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is three plus six times two minus six times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 15,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fifteen.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 18,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply six by two and six by zero",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 6 by 2 and 6 by 0, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 3 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 X 2 = 12; 6 X 0 = 0; Now we have 3 + 12 - 0; 3 + 12 = 15; Now we have 15 - 0 = 15"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 280,
	"Question" : "What is (0 + 7) X 4 + 8?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (zero plus seven) times four plus eight?",
	"Answer" : 36,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is thirty-six.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 84,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by four next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 36,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding zero and seven.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 0 to 7 before multiplying 4 with that sum, and then add 8 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "0 + 7 = 7; Now we have: 7 X 4 + 8; 7 X 4 = 28; Now we have 28 + 8 = 36"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 281,
	"Question" : "What is 3 + 7 X 0 + 9 X 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is three plus seven times zero plus nine times one?", 
	"Answer" : 12,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twelve.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 9,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply seven by zero and nine by one",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 7 by 0 and 9 by 1, and add the second product to the first. Then, add 3 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "7 X 0 = 0; 9 X 1 = 9; Now we have 3 + 0 + 9; 3 + 0 = 3; Now we have 3 + 9 = 12"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 282,
	"Question" : "What is 7 + (0 + 7) X 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is seven plus (zero plus seven) times one?", 
	"Answer" : 14,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fourteen.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 14,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by one next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 14,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding zero and seven.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 0 to 7 before multiplying 1 with that sum, and then add 7 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "0 + 7 = 7; Now we have:7 + 7 X 1; 7 X 1 = 7; Now we have 7 + 7 = 14"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 283,
	"Question" : "What is 6 + 7 X 1 + 8 X 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is six plus seven times one plus eight times three?", 
	"Answer" : 37,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is thirty-seven.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 37,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply seven by one and eight by three",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 7 by 1 and 8 by 3, and add the second product to the first. Then, add 6 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "7 X 1 = 7; 8 X 3 = 24; Now we have 6 + 7 + 24; 6 + 7 = 13; Now we have 13 + 24 = 37"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 284,
	"Question" : "What is (0 + 8) X 0 + 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (zero plus eight) times zero plus three?",
	"Answer" : 3,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is three.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 24,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by zero next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 3,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding zero and eight.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 0 to 8 before multiplying 0 with that sum, and then add 3 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "0 + 8 = 8; Now we have: 8 X 0 + 3; 8 X 0 = 0; Now we have 0 + 3 = 3"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 285,
	"Question" : "What is 3 + 6 X 4 - 7 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is three plus six times four minus seven times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 27,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-seven.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 36,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply six by four and seven by zero",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 6 by 4 and 7 by 0, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 3 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 X 4 = 24; 7 X 0 = 0; Now we have 3 + 24 - 0; 3 + 24 = 27; Now we have 27 - 0 = 27"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 286,
	"Question" : "What is 9 + (2 + 6) X 9?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is nine plus (two plus six) times nine?", 
	"Answer" : 81,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is eighty-one.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 153,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by nine next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 65,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding two and six.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 2 to 6 before multiplying 9 with that sum, and then add 9 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "2 + 6 = 8; Now we have:9 + 8 X 9; 8 X 9 = 72; Now we have 9 + 72 = 81"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 287,
	"Question" : "What is 4 + 5 X 0 + 8 X 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is four plus five times zero plus eight times four?", 
	"Answer" : 36,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is thirty-six.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 32,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply five by zero and eight by four",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 5 by 0 and 8 by 4, and add the second product to the first. Then, add 4 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 X 0 = 0; 8 X 4 = 32; Now we have 4 + 0 + 32; 4 + 0 = 4; Now we have 4 + 32 = 36"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 288,
	"Question" : "What is (1 + 5) X 2 + 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (one plus five) times two plus four?",
	"Answer" : 16,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is sixteen.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 36,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by two next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 15,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding one and five.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 1 to 5 before multiplying 2 with that sum, and then add 4 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "1 + 5 = 6; Now we have: 6 X 2 + 4; 6 X 2 = 12; Now we have 12 + 4 = 16"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 289,
	"Question" : "What is 2 + 8 X 4 - 9 X 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is two plus eight times four minus nine times one?", 
	"Answer" : 25,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-five.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 31,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply eight by four and nine by one",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 8 by 4 and 9 by 1, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 2 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "8 X 4 = 32; 9 X 1 = 9; Now we have 2 + 32 - 9; 2 + 32 = 34; Now we have 34 - 9 = 25"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 290,
	"Question" : "What is 5 + (0 + 6) X 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is five plus (zero plus six) times one?", 
	"Answer" : 11,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is eleven.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 11,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by one next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 11,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding zero and six.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 0 to 6 before multiplying 1 with that sum, and then add 5 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "0 + 6 = 6; Now we have:5 + 6 X 1; 6 X 1 = 6; Now we have 5 + 6 = 11"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 291,
	"Question" : "What is 1 + 7 X 0 + 5 X 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is one plus seven times zero plus five times one?", 
	"Answer" : 6,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is six.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 5,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply seven by zero and five by one",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 7 by 0 and 5 by 1, and add the second product to the first. Then, add 1 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "7 X 0 = 0; 5 X 1 = 5; Now we have 1 + 0 + 5; 1 + 0 = 1; Now we have 1 + 5 = 6"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 292,
	"Question" : "What is (0 + 7) X 8 + 8?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (zero plus seven) times eight plus eight?",
	"Answer" : 64,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is sixty-four.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 112,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by eight next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 64,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding zero and seven.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 0 to 7 before multiplying 8 with that sum, and then add 8 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "0 + 7 = 7; Now we have: 7 X 8 + 8; 7 X 8 = 56; Now we have 56 + 8 = 64"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 293,
	"Question" : "What is 8 + 8 X 3 + 8 X 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is eight plus eight times three plus eight times four?", 
	"Answer" : 64,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is sixty-four.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 80,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply eight by three and eight by four",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 8 by 3 and 8 by 4, and add the second product to the first. Then, add 8 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "8 X 3 = 24; 8 X 4 = 32; Now we have 8 + 24 + 32; 8 + 24 = 32; Now we have 32 + 32 = 64"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 294,
	"Question" : "What is (1 + 6) X 2 + 5?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (one plus six) times two plus five?",
	"Answer" : 19,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is nineteen.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 49,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by two next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 18,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding one and six.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 1 to 6 before multiplying 2 with that sum, and then add 5 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "1 + 6 = 7; Now we have: 7 X 2 + 5; 7 X 2 = 14; Now we have 14 + 5 = 19"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 295,
	"Question" : "What is 9 + 8 X 0 + 8 X 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is nine plus eight times zero plus eight times four?", 
	"Answer" : 41,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is forty-one.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 32,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply eight by zero and eight by four",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 8 by 0 and 8 by 4, and add the second product to the first. Then, add 9 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "8 X 0 = 0; 8 X 4 = 32; Now we have 9 + 0 + 32; 9 + 0 = 9; Now we have 9 + 32 = 41"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 296,
	"Question" : "What is 9 + (0 + 9) X 9?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is nine plus (zero plus nine) times nine?", 
	"Answer" : 90,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is ninety.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 162,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by nine next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 90,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding zero and nine.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 0 to 9 before multiplying 9 with that sum, and then add 9 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "0 + 9 = 9; Now we have:9 + 9 X 9; 9 X 9 = 81; Now we have 9 + 81 = 90"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 297,
	"Question" : "What is 4 + 8 X 3 - 7 X 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is four plus eight times three minus seven times three?", 
	"Answer" : 7,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is seven.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 15,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply eight by three and seven by three",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 8 by 3 and 7 by 3, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 4 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "8 X 3 = 24; 7 X 3 = 21; Now we have 4 + 24 - 21; 4 + 24 = 28; Now we have 28 - 21 = 7"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 298,
	"Question" : "What is (1 + 5) X 4 + 9?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (one plus five) times four plus nine?",
	"Answer" : 33,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is thirty-three.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 78,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by four next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 30,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding one and five.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 1 to 5 before multiplying 4 with that sum, and then add 9 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "1 + 5 = 6; Now we have: 6 X 4 + 9; 6 X 4 = 24; Now we have 24 + 9 = 33"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 299,
	"Question" : "What is 0 + 5 X 2 + 5 X 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is zero plus five times two plus five times three?", 
	"Answer" : 25,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-five.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 25,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply five by two and five by three",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 5 by 2 and 5 by 3, and add the second product to the first. Then, add 0 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 X 2 = 10; 5 X 3 = 15; Now we have 0 + 10 + 15; 0 + 10 = 10; Now we have 10 + 15 = 25"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 300,
	"Question" : "What is 8 + (2 + 6) X 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is eight plus (two plus six) times one?", 
	"Answer" : 16,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is sixteen.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 16,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by one next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 16,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding two and six.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 2 to 6 before multiplying 1 with that sum, and then add 8 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "2 + 6 = 8; Now we have:8 + 8 X 1; 8 X 1 = 8; Now we have 8 + 8 = 16"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 301,
	"Question" : "What is 7 + 8 X 2 + 9 X 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is seven plus eight times two plus nine times three?", 
	"Answer" : 50,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fifty.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 57,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply eight by two and nine by three",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 8 by 2 and 9 by 3, and add the second product to the first. Then, add 7 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "8 X 2 = 16; 9 X 3 = 27; Now we have 7 + 16 + 27; 7 + 16 = 23; Now we have 23 + 27 = 50"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 302,
	"Question" : "What is 0 + (1 + 8) X 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is zero plus (one plus eight) times three?", 
	"Answer" : 27,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-seven.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 27,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by three next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 25,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding one and eight.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 1 to 8 before multiplying 3 with that sum, and then add 0 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "1 + 8 = 9; Now we have:0 + 9 X 3; 9 X 3 = 27; Now we have 0 + 27 = 27"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 303,
	"Question" : "What is 1 + 6 X 4 - 6 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is one plus six times four minus six times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 25,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-five.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 28,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply six by four and six by zero",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 6 by 4 and 6 by 0, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 1 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 X 4 = 24; 6 X 0 = 0; Now we have 1 + 24 - 0; 1 + 24 = 25; Now we have 25 - 0 = 25"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 304,
	"Question" : "What is (1 + 5) X 4 + 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (one plus five) times four plus three?",
	"Answer" : 27,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-seven.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 42,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by four next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 24,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding one and five.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 1 to 5 before multiplying 4 with that sum, and then add 3 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "1 + 5 = 6; Now we have: 6 X 4 + 3; 6 X 4 = 24; Now we have 24 + 3 = 27"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 305,
	"Question" : "What is 1 + 7 X 2 - 9 X 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is one plus seven times two minus nine times one?", 
	"Answer" : 6,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is six.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 7,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply seven by two and nine by one",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 7 by 2 and 9 by 1, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 1 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "7 X 2 = 14; 9 X 1 = 9; Now we have 1 + 14 - 9; 1 + 14 = 15; Now we have 15 - 9 = 6"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 306,
	"Question" : "What is (2 + 6) X 8 + 5?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (two plus six) times eight plus five?",
	"Answer" : 69,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is sixty-nine.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 104,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by eight next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 55,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding two and six.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 2 to 6 before multiplying 8 with that sum, and then add 5 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "2 + 6 = 8; Now we have: 8 X 8 + 5; 8 X 8 = 64; Now we have 64 + 5 = 69"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 307,
	"Question" : "What is 0 + 5 X 1 + 9 X 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is zero plus five times one plus nine times one?", 
	"Answer" : 14,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fourteen.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 14,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply five by one and nine by one",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 5 by 1 and 9 by 1, and add the second product to the first. Then, add 0 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 X 1 = 5; 9 X 1 = 9; Now we have 0 + 5 + 9; 0 + 5 = 5; Now we have 5 + 9 = 14"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 308,
	"Question" : "What is (2 + 7) X 8 + 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (two plus seven) times eight plus three?",
	"Answer" : 75,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is seventy-five.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 99,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by eight next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 61,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding two and seven.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 2 to 7 before multiplying 8 with that sum, and then add 3 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "2 + 7 = 9; Now we have: 9 X 8 + 3; 9 X 8 = 72; Now we have 72 + 3 = 75"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 309,
	"Question" : "What is 3 + 7 X 3 - 5 X 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is three plus seven times three minus five times one?", 
	"Answer" : 19,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is nineteen.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 25,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply seven by three and five by one",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 7 by 3 and 5 by 1, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 3 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "7 X 3 = 21; 5 X 1 = 5; Now we have 3 + 21 - 5; 3 + 21 = 24; Now we have 24 - 5 = 19"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 310,
	"Question" : "What is 5 + (2 + 5) X 7?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is five plus (two plus five) times seven?", 
	"Answer" : 54,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fifty-four.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 84,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by seven next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 42,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding two and five.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 2 to 5 before multiplying 7 with that sum, and then add 5 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "2 + 5 = 7; Now we have:5 + 7 X 7; 7 X 7 = 49; Now we have 5 + 49 = 54"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 311,
	"Question" : "What is 3 + 8 X 0 + 7 X 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is three plus eight times zero plus seven times four?", 
	"Answer" : 31,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is thirty-one.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 28,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply eight by zero and seven by four",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 8 by 0 and 7 by 4, and add the second product to the first. Then, add 3 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "8 X 0 = 0; 7 X 4 = 28; Now we have 3 + 0 + 28; 3 + 0 = 3; Now we have 3 + 28 = 31"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 312,
	"Question" : "What is (1 + 7) X 4 + 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (one plus seven) times four plus four?",
	"Answer" : 36,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is thirty-six.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 64,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by four next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 33,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding one and seven.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 1 to 7 before multiplying 4 with that sum, and then add 4 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "1 + 7 = 8; Now we have: 8 X 4 + 4; 8 X 4 = 32; Now we have 32 + 4 = 36"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 313,
	"Question" : "What is 0 + 5 X 4 + 8 X 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is zero plus five times four plus eight times four?", 
	"Answer" : 52,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fifty-two.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 52,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply five by four and eight by four",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 5 by 4 and 8 by 4, and add the second product to the first. Then, add 0 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 X 4 = 20; 8 X 4 = 32; Now we have 0 + 20 + 32; 0 + 20 = 20; Now we have 20 + 32 = 52"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 314,
	"Question" : "What is (0 + 6) X 4 + 8?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (zero plus six) times four plus eight?",
	"Answer" : 32,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is thirty-two.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 72,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by four next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 32,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding zero and six.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 0 to 6 before multiplying 4 with that sum, and then add 8 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "0 + 6 = 6; Now we have: 6 X 4 + 8; 6 X 4 = 24; Now we have 24 + 8 = 32"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 315,
	"Question" : "What is 8 + 9 X 2 - 5 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is eight plus nine times two minus five times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 26,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-six.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 34,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply nine by two and five by zero",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 9 by 2 and 5 by 0, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 8 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 X 2 = 18; 5 X 0 = 0; Now we have 8 + 18 - 0; 8 + 18 = 26; Now we have 26 - 0 = 26"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 316,
	"Question" : "What is (3 + 6) X 2 + 9?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (three plus six) times two plus nine?",
	"Answer" : 27,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-seven.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 99,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by two next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 24,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding three and six.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 3 to 6 before multiplying 2 with that sum, and then add 9 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 + 6 = 9; Now we have: 9 X 2 + 9; 9 X 2 = 18; Now we have 18 + 9 = 27"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 317,
	"Question" : "What is 1 + 8 X 4 - 8 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is one plus eight times four minus eight times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 33,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is thirty-three.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 36,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply eight by four and eight by zero",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 8 by 4 and 8 by 0, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 1 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "8 X 4 = 32; 8 X 0 = 0; Now we have 1 + 32 - 0; 1 + 32 = 33; Now we have 33 - 0 = 33"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 318,
	"Question" : "What is 4 + (0 + 6) X 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is four plus (zero plus six) times three?", 
	"Answer" : 22,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-two.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 30,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember that once you've done what's inside the parentheses, multiply by three next.",
		"Common Mistake 2" : 22,
		"Spoken Explanation 2" : "Remember to do what's inside the parentheses first, by adding zero and six.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 0 to 6 before multiplying 3 with that sum, and then add 4 to that product.",
		"Written General Feedback" : "0 + 6 = 6; Now we have:4 + 6 X 3; 6 X 3 = 18; Now we have 4 + 18 = 22"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 319,
	"Question" : "What is 5 + 8 X 4 - 7 X 2?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is five plus eight times four minus seven times two?", 
	"Answer" : 23,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-three.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 38,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply eight by four and seven by two",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 8 by 4 and 7 by 2, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 5 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "8 X 4 = 32; 7 X 2 = 14; Now we have 5 + 32 - 14; 5 + 32 = 37; Now we have 37 - 14 = 23"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 2,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

]
